

PROFILE

I am currently pursuing a bachelor's degree in Computer Science Engineering (CSE) from Chandigarh University. I am currently trying to explore my knowledge in fields of Machine learning and Artificial Intelligence. And know about Front-End website development.

I have also worked as part-time Freelance content writer since December, 2018. Just looking forward to explore more and more and gain great knowledge and experience.

CONTACT

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/atul-jha-80b71b1a7

EMAIL:

jhaatul915@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Badminton Writing imaginary stories Listening music's

ATUL JHA

https://www.linkedin.com/in/atul-jha-80b71b1a7

EDUCATION

Chandigarh University

Pursing Bachelors in Computer Science 2019 - 2023

WORK EXPERIENCE

Innovator's Hub

September, 2020 - February, 2021

Working for Innovators hub as Student representative and also IH Networking team member. Trying to work on different- different ideas with team to enhance my knowledge and team work skills.

Pioneer Club

January, 2021 - July, 2021

This University club is totally dedicated to patents, research papers and hosting events related to our Niches. I am working as a team coordinator.

Dexignare

December, 2020 - present

This is open community dedicated to UI/UX related topic for promoting and helping newbie developers to gain some quality knowledge. I am working as digital marketer in this team.

SKILLS

Front-End Webdevelopment (HTML, CSS, Javascript and Node JS) Basic C++ for Data structure and Algorithm Python programming Machine learning for data analysis and plotting

Currently learning:-ROS in Ubuntu (Robot operating system)

PROJECT WORKED/ WORKING:-

Worked on Titanic dataset for plotting data graphs and predicting the survival rate of on-board passengers.

E-Commerce website template

Partially automated laptop on voice command.

Working for patent idea generation in Innovators hub

